<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollsiRecycler</string>
    <string name="recycler_view">Recycler View</string>
    <string name="scroll_view">Scroll View</string>

    <string name="long_text_ahead"> The folklore surrounding black cats varies from culture to culture.The Scots believe that a strange black cats arrival to the home signifies prosperity.
        In Celtic mythology, a fairy known as the Cat Sìth takes the form of a black cat. Black cats are also considered good luck in the rest of Britain and Japan.[4] Furthermore, it is
        believed that a lady who owns a black cat will have many suitors.[5] In Western history, black cats have often been looked upon as a symbol of evil omens, specifically being
        suspected of being the familiars of witches, or actually shape-shifting witches themselves. Most of Europe considers the black cat a symbol of bad luck, particularly if one walks
        across the path in front of a person, which is believed to be an omen of misfortune and death. In Germany, some believe that black cats crossing a persons path from right to left,
        is a bad omen. But from left to right, the cat is granting favorable times.[6] In the United Kingdom it is commonly considered that a black cat crossing a persons path is a good omen.
        The black cat in folklore has been able to change into human shape to act as a spy or courier for witches or demons. When the Pilgrims arrived at Plymouth Rock, they brought with them
        a devout faith in the Bible. They also brought a deepening suspicion of anything deemed of Satan and were a deeply suspicious group. They viewed the black cat as a companion, or a
        familiar to witches. Anyone caught with a black cat would be severely punished or even killed. They viewed the black cat as part demon and part sorcery. These superstitions led people
        to kill black cats. There is no evidence from England of regular large-scale massacres of "satanic" cats, or of burning them in midsummer bonfires, as sometimes occurred elsewhere in
        Europe. </string>

    <string name= "cats_introduction"> This is an awesome black cat! </string>

</resources>
